rightrelevance.com 2015-06-24

# Privacy Policy Right Relevance

At Right Relevance, we strongly believe in securing user privacy and take all reasonable measures to protect user information, esp. personally identifiable information (PII), against unauthorized access or use. As part of our business and offerings, we apply machine learning and other data analysis techniques to learn more about our users to be able to provide a continuously improving user experience including better personalization. We employ all reasonable practices to ensure that these analytics along with user PII are well protected. 

You have to agree to the Privacy Policy below for us to be able to provide you access to our software and services including our websites, APIs and mobile applications. 

#### USER INFORMATION COLLECTION

Personally Identifiable Information(PII)  
When using the Right Relevance logged in experience and engaging via sharing, retweeting, replying etc. from our website and applications, you are required to connect your Twitter, Facebook and/or LinkedIn accounts. This enables us to obtain the your name, email address, location, interests etc. depending on the information on your profile and security and privacy settings. If you do not wish to disclose this data, please adjust your social network security and privacy settings accordingly. 

Non Personally Identifiable Information(PII)  

When you use the Right Relevance website or applications, we may collect non personally identifiable information like browser type, browser version, referring URL, operating system, language preference etc. This information is used in aggregates to understand our users better to enable us to build a better user experience. 

#### COOKIES

Right Relevance uses browser cookies to save your login session and application preferences. For this reason, you must have cookies enabled when you use our site, otherwise you will not be able to enjoy the logged in experience and all the associated goodness. Users who do not wish to have cookies placed on their browsers can set their browsers to refuse cookies and still use the limited non-logged-in experience. 

#### USER DATA ACCESS AND PROTECTION

Right Relevance discloses user data including PII only to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations only if they have agreed to not disclose it to others and need to know that information to provide services on our behalf. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country and by using Right Relevance applications and services you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Right Relevance will not disclose, sell or rent your data to anyone else other than the above listed. 

Right Relevance discloses personally identifiable information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request. We may disclose your information to a third party where we believe, in good faith, that it is desirable to do so for the purposes of a civil action, criminal investigation, or other legal matter. 

Right Relevance may use the email address of registered users to send emails to update them about new features, request for feedback or make them aware of the latest happenings in the topics of their interests. You may unsubscribe from our communications by notifying Right Relevance (currently via [social@rightrelevance.com](mailto:social@rightrelevance.com)) that you no longer wish to receive information from us and we will endeavor to remove you from our email subscriptions and/or user database depending on your request. 

#### PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES

Right Relevance may change its Privacy Policy from time to time and will keep this page updated. We encourage you to frequent this page regularly to be aware of any changes. Your continued use of the Right Relevance sites, services or applications will be constituted as acceptance of our Privacy Policy and any amendments. 

#### Last Updated: August 15th 2014
